<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Litmus\'17</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_first">Call For volunteers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_comingsoon">Comingsoon</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mainpage">Litmus17</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="link">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=itmvu.litmus17</string>
    <string name="frwd">Share this app through</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">Events Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Register Your Self</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t1">Fury of Tracks</string>
    <string name="t1des">Design the fastest and the shrewdest car and put on your set-belts to facFe a white-knuckling race through the roughest arena! From the makers of \‘LITMUS\’, here\’s another thrilling real time all-terrain racing competition! Let\’s put your car-designing abilities and your car\’s, the strength, power and efficiency off to test.\n\nIt’s the fury of tracks for the roaring cars. We present you the <b>AUTOMOPHILES</b> for your very own creation.</string>
    <string name="t1rules">A.Team Size: Max. 4 persons \n\nB.The competition is only for autonomous robots (remotely controlled), no manual robot will be permitted to enter. The robot can be powered  are electrically only.\n\nC.The electric voltage between 2 points anywhere in the robot should not be more than 20 V DC at any point of time. \n\nD.All efforts must be made to protect battery terminals from a direct short and causing a battery fire, failure to do so will cause direct disqualification.\n\nE.Use of damaged, non-leak proof batteries may lead to disqualification. \n\nF.change of battery will not be allowed during the match.\n\nG.A robot is declared victorious with the least time.\n\nH.Only 1 checkpoint skip (time + 30sec) and 3 hand touch are allowed. \n\nI.Track width will be 20 cm.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t2">Code To Win</string>
    <string name="t2rules">A.Each team should have two members.\n\nB. There will be 2 rounds, one easy and another one little typical.\n\nC. There should not be any use of unfair means, if this happens then the team will be disqualified.\n\nD. Winners will be decided on the basis of time taken in making up with the assigned tasks.</string>
    <string name="t2desp">It\’s time to step out of your comfort zone. This event is going to be a test of your coding skill, under pressure.\n\nRun your brain and your fingers simultaneously.\n\n \“Most good programmers do programming not because they expect to get paid or get adulation by the public, but because it is fun to program.\”\n\n– Linus Torvalds (Finnish American, software engineer and hacker, principal force behind the development of the Linux kernel)</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t3">FIERY FIGHTERS</string>
    <string name="t3desp">\“Let the metal do the talking\”\n\nPassionate about Bots? Or you just like to watch things get crushed from fierce competition? The path to glory passes through the alley of destruction, lethal combats, violent bots, and flying blades! Merge your technical know-how with the ferocious gladiator in you! Make your bot fight for the ultimate glory or land up in the junk yard!\n\nFight smart, be patient\n\nLet your Robo\’s prove themselves to be the most powerful and reliable warriors!\n\nLet them make the havoc in their enemy\’s town. See you in the arena</string>
    <string name="t3rules">A.Team Size: Max. 4 persons \n\nB.Two ROBOTs compete in a head-to-head match following the basics of wrestling.\n\nC.ROBOTs should be wireless or wired remote controlled. \n\nD.Like wrestling, the ROBOTs are given three full minutes for a round, in which either one of the ROBOTs is knocked out or the match time runs out, and judges decide the winner.\n\nE.The ROBOT should fit in a box of dimensions 400mm*400mm*400mm excluding the external control device dimensions.\n\nF.The weight limit of the ROBOT is 20 kg maximum including battery  Grabbing and throwing mechanism is allowed.\n\nG.The robot will be disqualified if any parts fail &amp;fall off in the arena and is unable to move for 10 seconds.\n\nH.The team destroying the opponents wiring circuitry intentionally or even by mistake  during the time of war will be disqualified.\n\nI.The decision of the Core Committee will be considered final and indisputable.\n\nJ.The Core Committee has the right to change any of the rules at any time.\n\nK.If the machine remains immobile for respectable time then on the spot decision will be taken by the Core Committee.</string>


    <string name="title_activity_t4">SPEEDING MACHINES</string>
    <string name="t4desp">Strength isn\’t everything, are you fast enough?\n\nWhen you think you know it all, it\’s sure a sign you don’t. There is no place for arrogance and complacency in racing because you are up there one minute and on your backside the next. So all you ingenious engineers-to-be out there have an opportunity to Muster here and not only witness, but also be a part of the exhibit of sheer efficacy of brilliance. \n\n Fasten your wheels and just smash the finish line before any other of your clone.\n\n</string>
    <string name="t4rules">A. Team Size: Max. 4 persons.\n\nB. The track consists of different hurdle, which makes it difficult for a normal ROBOT to successfully cross them. \n\nC. Thus it requires a composite capability of having optimum speed and the torque to be a winner in a specifically given time duration. \n\nD. The ROBOT also requires the proper steering mechanism which will be able to pass through the curves.\n\nE. The ROBOT dimensions should not exceed 200*200*200 mm excluding the control device dimensions.\n\nF. The weight limit of the ROBOT is 6 kg maximum including battery and 4 kg excluding.\n\nG. The ROBOT may use wireless remote. Readymade wireless remote control units may be used.\n\nH. Maximum voltage between any two points on the ROBOT must not exceed 20 V dc. any dimension according to the ROBOT.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t5">FLYING WARRIORS</string>
    <string name="t5desp">Let your sky dazzle the heads, around the event.\n\nThe beat skipping copter competition is fetched to you by LITMUS conjured by the hypnotic city weather and energetic roaring crowd. When the propellers call to complain of their dormancy there is no such thing left which can be called as defeat.\n\n Hover your talent and beat the air. Release them and enjoy the mayhem!!\n\n Design and make a wireless remote controlled flying platform to complete obstacle course without crash in minimum time.\n\n Consisting of loops, bends, underpass, overpass and secret paths placed in random sequence along an aerial track. \n\n</string>
    <string name="t5rules">A.Participant must arrive at the event before 30mins.\n\nB.Flight time for a run is defined as the time taken by the drone to follow the mentioned path.\n\nC.A maximum time of 5 minutes from set up to exit from Arena will be given to complete the circuit.\n\nD.The drone has to be kept on the start zone in the starting itself.\n\nE.The timer will start from the moment the countdown finish.\n\nF.The timer will stop only when the drone finally comes to Start zone.\n\nG.Battery voltage should not exceed 3.7 v, and the construction of the copter won’t exceed the size of 40x40(cm). </string>

    <string name="title_activity_t6">Construo</string>
    <string name="t6desp">So it\’s finally the time for some fun and crazy team work\n\nHave you been an artistic and a working mind, do you think you can come up with anything if you are given on newspaper, do you think you can work in team?!!\n\nThen come on mates, it\’s time to build your very own scraper from the scrap, because here the waste paper can make you some worthy stuff.\n\nSo enrol have fun, because you have nothing to waste!\n\nBe a construo warrior….\n\n</string>
    <string name="t6rules">A.a maximum of team of 4 will be allowed. \n\nB.The team will be provided with the limited material for making their own paper tower.\n\nC.Their will be a limited time to complete with your tower. </string>

    <string name="title_activity_t7">Bridge The Gap</string>
    <string name="t7desp">Across gulfs and rivers, between people and countries, bridges break down separation and foster connectedness.\n\n The world has gone at its heights to reach the sky. Your problem here is to bridge the gap which exists between where you are now and the goal you intend to reach. So do it with closed minds though careful dissection of ideas and solid presentation of fact. Here is your chance to build structures with your own techniques and skills and make the marvels of engineering!! \n\n </string>
    <string name="t7rules">A.Each team should be of maximum 4 members.\n\nB. Materials to be used: Popsicle sticks, Fevicol , Hard board, thread.\n\nC. Use of any other adhesive, etc. is prohibited and participants using it will be disqualified from the event.\n\nD. All the models must be taken for the self-weighing during the specified period of time (any entry after that won’t be accepted and would be disqualified).\n\nE. No changes in the model after the self-weighing would be allowed and any team doing so without the permission of the core committee member would be disqualified.\n\nF. The decision of the judges and core committee will be final regarding any discrepancy on the spot or before the event.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t8">Shift To Beat</string>
    <string name="t8desp">One of the most exciting events of LITMUS 2017 is this LAN Gaming event. Come and test your gaming skills over the LAN by going head to head against your opponents and show off your gaming skills. Participate in this event by playing the games NFS Most Wanted, and Counter Strike and take away the cash award.\n\nNFS Most Wanted:\n\nGot Speed? \n\n Try out your driving skills against your opponents in the asphalt burning NFS Most Wanted. Drive your way through to finish first and win the cash pot! Steer your throttle to win! </string>
    <string name="t8rules">A.single player registration.\n\nB.Players will be shortlisted in the next round.\n\nC.There are three round.\n\nD.Players will only compete if they have qualified same number of rounds.\n\nE.Participant members are  allowed to bring their own Headphones, Keyboards.\n\nF.Joy sticks not allowed.\n\nG.The decision of the judges and core committee will be final.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t9">Hit it to Win it</string>
    <string name="t9desp">\“STICK TOGETHER TEAM\”\n\nThe Ultimate Team game! The champ of military strategy, here\’s your chance..\n\n Join us with your Counter Strike Clan and go against the opponent clans to be the King of the Counter Strike Ring!!!!\n\n</string>
    <string name="t9rules">A.A team should consist max of 5 members and minimum 4.\n\nB. Every clan should have their team name.\n\nC. All matches are played using the max round 5 scoring system by default.\n\nD. Every match will be competition with another clan.\n\nE. A clan will disqualify if found using cheats.\n\nF. All matches needed to be played using Counter Strike v1.6.\n\nG. Both clans get to choose if they start as T or CT.\n\nH. Every winning game will earn you a reward point.\n\nI. Winners will be decided on final score.\n\nJ. The decision of the judges and core committee will be final.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t10">Folder Maze</string>
    <string name="t10desp">In the folder maze game the player is supposed click though the folders opening the txt file in every folder and doing as the written text says. Txt file may contain questions, riddles, source to another. The maze will get harder as you go deep into the labyrinth of folders. Just remember one thing: Do as the text says and you will reach the goal in the least time.</string>
    <string name="t10rules">A. The game consist of 3 rounds.\n\nB. Player who finishes fastest wins, Top 3 winners will be rewarded.\n\nC. Folders will contain text files which are supposed to be read to move further closer to the goal.\n\nD. Folders may lead the player to another folder or back to previous folders depending on the difficulty level of round.\n\nE. The decision of the judges and core committee will be final.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_t11">Reclamation</string>
    <string name="t11desp">Creativity is your imagination and your talent coming out of your brain. So it\’s time to bring your imagination to reality, show case your talent and bring forth your ideas to the world.\n\nThe trash can make you the winner, ready to be partners with it?\n\nParticipate to explore your mindboggling skills.\n\n</string>
    <string name="t11rules">A.Team Size: Max. 4 persons.\n\nB. The participant of any team cannot enter the area of the other teams. \n\nC. If there is any damage to the tools provided or instruments, then the team to which the instrument was given would be liable to pay for the damage. \n\nD. Workshop facilities will be provided to the participants. \n\nE. Participants need to have a basic  idea about workshop safety and operational precautions.\n\nF. The safety of the participant solely depends on the participant himself.\n\nG. There will be no restriction on the type of mechanism used by the team to perform the task provided no other rule is violated.\n\nH. The team violating the above rules will be disqualified.\n\nI. Judge\'s decision shall be treated as final and binding on all. </string>

    <string name="title_activity_t12">ARTRIVIA</string>
    <string name="t12desp">You can\’t use up creativity. The more you use the more you have.\n\nChange the dimension of your art get along with our Artrivia a new way of portraying your creativity on a display. Let the clicks and the movement be advanced, let your imagination and your work prove your worth.\n\nWelcome to our very own first art event of designing posters on Photoshop, do you have that, on the spot skills? are you the art freak? get your tools and just show your talent on the new canvas.\n\n</string>
    <string name="t12rules">1. Document size should be International paper (A4) \n\n2. Internet can be used to download content related to Poster Making.\n\n3. Time allotted for Poster making is one Hour.\n\n4. Number of Topics 5\n\n5. Team Should Be of Maximum 2 Members.\n\n </string>

    <string name="title_activity_t13">"HYDRAULIC ROBO RACE "</string>
    <string name="t13desp">Is pneumatic your piece of cake, do your bot have that haste to beat others.\n\nWitness the fight under the pressure, our very own racing event with pressure in its nerves. Be a part of neat fight and thrill because technology makes everyone roll-on.\n\nDevelop the canniest robo and guide it to win.\n\nSee you at the track…!\n\n</string>

    <string name="title_activity_c1">Girls Gully Cricket</string>
    <string name="c1desp">India doesn\’t need a world cup to stimulate them to play cricket. We have been playing cricket since we remember our friends and siblings.\n\nSo pretty girls out there, here’s the turf for your excitement and joy, cricket with a version of madness, screams and laughter.\n\nHits and misses, six and catches there’s a lot on the plate, so be ready, and let the ball soar high, hit hard.\n\n</string>


    <string name="title_activity_c2">Cricket</string>
    <string name="c2desp">Cricket and life are alike, every ball equals every minute, every shot, equals an opportunity, and every wicket is an obstacle.\n\nDo you have a team to be victorious with a sport that goes with the thrill in its core?\n\nRegister in the game of gentlemen, enjoy the madness and let your talent be in front.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c3">Volley Ball</string>
    <string name="c3desp" formatted="false" >Be ready to face the sun, and don’t let that be the excuse of your failure, because they say volleyball is 90% heart, 10% skill, and 10% passion, you always give 110% on the field no matter what.\n\nLet your serve pierce the opponent\’s confidence, jump and smash it.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c4">FootBall</string>
    <string name="c4desp">In a football game there is one TEAM and one DREAM and that is to win the day! So let\’s fight on!\n\nBehind every kick of the ball, there is always a thought. Suit up for the combat of 5-a side football match, and let the goal post be shattered with your power or let your moves get crushed with the defence.\n\nSo boys, gear up, pace your skills and let the whistle blow loud…!\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c5">Basket Ball</string>
    <string name="c5desp">Dribble, shoot, rebound and score…\n\n\“I have failed over and over again in my life, and that is why I succeed\”- Michael Jordan\n\nHere’s the sport of chances and perfection, you better be focused so you don\’t miss, let the people cheer on your dunks, let your score win your team.\n\nSo boys in shorts, make every chance a shot.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c6">Carrom</string>
    <string name="c6desp">So the strike and pocket game is here for the board game lovers.\n\nCarrom is much deeper, much more strategic, much more skill rewarding and generally a much better game.\n\nA game which brings fun and togetherness, the ups and downs in each move, and the fun-fight for the queen, here\'s all for your striking abilities, participate and let\’s see who gets the queen.\n\nSee you at the other corner soon\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c7">ATHLETICS</string>
    <string name="c7desp">There is no one giant step that does it, it’s a lot of little steps. It teaches us to challenge ourselves. It teaches us to push beyond where we thought we could go. It helps us to find what we are made of. This is what we do that is what it\’s all about.\n\nGet your running shoes and let them feel the dust, let them taste the win, give yourself a new bench-mark. So let\’s start with \“why I am doing this?\” And end with \“When can I do this again?\”\n\nLitmus presents the sprinting feast for the running lovers.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c8">Chess</string>
    <string name="c8desp">All that matters on chess-board is never to give up!\n\nLife is like a game of chess, to win you have to move. Knowing which move to make comes with in-sight and knowledge.\n\nChess is everything: art, science and sport. Your smartness and wits will be on a joy-ride, do you have that cleverness to dodge the defeat or we say \“CHECK-MATE\”.\n\nGet yourself in the event and let’s see who stays in and wins the battle of mind and reflexes.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_abtus">About Litmus\'17</string>

    <string name="abtus1">Due to inundating creativity and thirst for innovation of our students and with the constant guidance of our unparalleled faculty, LITMUS is all set for this year’s edition. Keeping in mind our core values of working as a team with integrity and professionalism, LITMUS has grown a lot from last year to become one of the most popular and awaited techno-management events in the city. Reaching out to students, industry and the society in general, LITMUS 2017 promises to be bigger than the last edition!\n\nEnroll and feel the zest..!\n\n</string>
    <string name="abtc">Sports don’t build character they reveal it \n\nLitmus presents you a 2-day nail-biting, sports action with full of excitement sportsmanship and fierce competition to emerge the best among all.\n\nWe bring cricket, football, volleyball, basketball, chess, Carrom, athletic events, table-tennis and gully-cricket.\n\nEnroll yourselves and enter this Chakravyuh and emerge victorious.\n\n</string>
    <string name="abtt">Technology is best when it brings people together \n\nA Carnival for the tech-enthusiasts who believe in making something efficient and worth, who believe in expanding the knowledge, who believe in experiencing the real-outcomes, who have the guts to face the competition, who believe learning outside the class as well.\n\nThis is the place for them…\n\nA two day tech bonanza for the people who have vision to compete and win something great in their field.\n\nLitmus welcomes everyone with warm heart…\n\nEnjoy.Explore.Learn\n\n</string>
    <string name="abtk">Remember this moment.Cherish the story.Celebrate this life\n\nThe annual day of the Litmus 2017, comprising of culture, innovators, experience, art, fun and madness.\n\nThe very own party celebration for the college students, to come along and celebrate the joy of life and spread happiness, because they say a good life is a collection of happy moments.\n\nWe believe in creating memories that lasts long, we end this day to come back better and bigger and with double the eagerness and fun.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contactus">Contact Us</string>


    <string name="g1">Dr. Gautam Patel \n+91 9574007671 \ngautamp\@itmuniversity.org \n\nMr. Ravindra Prajapati \n+91 9574005017 \nravindrap\@itmuniversity.org \n\nMr. Gulshan Kumar \n+91 9737911184 \ngulshank\@itm.edu \n\nMr. Manoj bhambhu \n+91 7046453657 \nmanojb\@itmuniversity.org \n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_c9">Table Tennis</string>
    <string name="c9desp">Hustle and hit and never quit.\n\nIt is a perfect combination of violent action taking place in an atmosphere of total tranquillity. Be the ball and dominate the options over and out. Enjoy and play the sport with utmost care.\n\nPing-Pong is all the way waiting for your serves and smash.\n\n</string>

    <string name="c1rules">a)Registration procedure will be same as that applied for boys. \n\nb)Teams would be formed consisting of 6 players each.\n\nc)Rest all the rules will be known to you on the day of match\n\n</string>
    <string name="c2rules">a)Registration will be done only on Official Webpage.\n\nb)Minimum Number of Players per Team: 11.\n\nc)Each innings will be of 8 over\’s.\n\nd)Final match will be of 10 over’s.\n\ne)Matches should be played from 15th to 17st February2015.\n\nf)Teams should be divided in 2 groups for knock out matches.\n\ng)Final match would be played on 17thFebruary.\n\nh)Rest all the rules will be disclosed to you on the day of match.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c3rules">a)Participant should carry Identity-card.\n\nb)Minimum number of  Players per Team: 6.\n\nc)11 points of 3 set will be played at knock out basis.\n\nd)Rest all the rules will be disclosed to you on the day of match.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c4rules">a)Team should consists of only 5 players. (One Goalkeeper &amp; 4 players)\n\nb)Half time at 15 Minutes.\n\nc)Participant should bring their own kit.\n\nd)Referee\'s decision will be final and binding.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c5rules">a)Participant should carry Identity-card.\n\nb) Number of Players per Team: 6\n\nc)6 minutes per quarter at knock out stages and final will be of 8 minutes.\n\nd)4 Quarter will be played at knock out basis.\n\ne)Rules will be according Basketball Federation of India, New Delhi.\n\nf)Rest all the rules will be disclosed to you on the day of match.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c6rules">a)ID card is mandatory for each player.\n\nb)Match will be played at knock out basis.\n\nc)Rest all the rules will be known to you on the day of match.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c7rules">a)ID card is mandatory for each player\n\nb)These are following events:- \n\n 1. 100 metere \n\n 2. 200 meter \n\n 3. 400 meter \n\n 4. Relay Race (400*4) \n\nc)Events will be held at qualifying stages, according to that best 2 athlete of each group will qualify for final race.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c8rules">a)ID card is mandatory for each player.\n\nb)Match will be played at knock out basis.\n\nc)All FIDE rules are applicable.\n\nd)For classical chess, match time will be of 1.5 hours for each.\n\n</string>
    <string name="c9rules">a)3 set of 11 points will be played at knock out stages.\n\nb)Semifinal &amp; final will be 5 sets of 11 point each.\n\v   nc)Rules as per the Table Tennis Federation of India.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sp">Sponsorship</string>

    <string name="spsh">Litmus\’17 is student driven fest. The fest open opportunities and avenues for the students to explore their talent and skills and showcase it hence forth enhancing their personality.\n\nIndustries Companies brands owners are cordially invited for their generous support to young birds of ITM VOCATIONAL UNIVERSITY in the form of sponsorship.\n\n</string>

    <string name="spsh1">Below are the Benefits of sponsoring ITM VOCATIONAL UNIVERSITY fest Litmus 2017 </string>
    <string name="spsh2">• Expected attendees – 1000/day 2000+(on 19/02/2017 include students ) \n\n•	 Targets age group 18-40 years\n\n• 5 days events  2 days for sports fest 2 days for technical event  1 day cultural fest and Dj night\n\n• Prioritize to give full exposure to the event on Social media platform.\n\n• A nice and spacious venue- University campus for events and University mini stadium for cultural fest and DJ night.\n\n• Giveaways and swags for attendees. Certificates to the attendees.\n\n•	Dedicated sponsors’ booth/kiosk.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_m1">PAINT YOUR IMAGINATION</string>
    <string name="m1desp">Face Painting\n\nGlass Painting\n\nT-Shirt Painting\n\nFlowerpot Painting\n\nGraffiti\n\nIt\’s time to let your imagination run wild and be creative. Paint face, glass, t-shirt, flowerpot or do Grafity(Wall Paint). Bring your imagination to reality and turn the world into your very own canvas.\n\n</string>
    <string name="m1rules">• Each participant is required to bring in their own colour paint, spray paint bottles (for graffiti) &amp; material (Paint Brush etc.) Choice of colours, paint brush number etc rests with participant.\n\n•Registration: Contestants must register for a selected category or multiple categories at least 1 day prior to the beginning of the competition.\n\n•Contestants and models must be in the competition area when competition begins Contestants/models entering late will be disqualified. \n\n•Full Face will have a 30 minute time limit. and other painting time will have 1 hour.\n\n•All painting will be done in front of a live audience. There will be no interaction with the competitors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="title_activity_m2">Documentary Film</string>
    <string name="m2desp">Grab your camera and start filming.\n\nYou can film yourself or someone else , you can film anywhere around you, film your home ,your work, your family and friends.\n\nTheme: \n\n •	Smoking kills/ ill effect of chewing tobacco \n\n• Pollution\n\n• Population\n\n• Female securities\n\n• Indian political system\n\n• Corruption\n\n</string>
    <string name="m2rules">• You must announce only the title of your presentation and names of participants.\n\n• Documentaries may not exceed ten minutes in length.\n\n• You will be allowed five minutes to set up and five minutes to remove equipment.\n\n• Timing begins when the first visual image appears and/or the first sound is heard. Audio and visual leads will be counted in the time limit.\n\n• Timing ends when the last visual image or sound of the presentation concludes (including credits).\n\n• NOTE: Use your setup time to prepare your documentary for presentation, adjust volume, etc.\n\n•Internet access may not be available.\n\n•You must provide the narration, voice-over, and dramatization. Only those student(s) listed as entrants may participate in the production.\n\n</string>

    <string name="title_activity_m3">Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="m3desp">Let your inner Indiana jones come out to go on a exciting hunt for treasure. Get ready for mind boggling riddles and puzzle. If you seek a fun-filled team building activity, you’re at right place.</string>
    <string name="m3rules">• The goal of the game is to lead the seekers through a set of clues that takes them from place to place to find a treasure.\n\n• The \“seekers\” need to read each clue they find and figure out the next location.\n\n• You must comply with all Official Rules, Eligibility, Terms and Conditions in order to remain eligible. Failure to do so will result in immediate disqualification from the competition\n\n• only 5 members allowed in a team.\n\n• Minimum time taken to solve mystery will be declare winner.\n\n</string>

    <string name="title_activity_m4">" AD-Selfie"</string>
    <string name="m4desp">\“Self-Serve Advertisement\” \n\nAD Selfie is a self-portrait photograph, typically taken with a digital camera or camera phone held in the hand or supported by a Selfie stick with a product and self-framed tagline. Grew your imagination by being Brand Ambassador of any product and add tagline to your product.</string>
    <string name="m4rules">• Participant must registered themselves at registration desk.\n\n• Select a product of your own choice, take your Selfie and edit a picture by adding tagline. (Your Picture + Selfie + New framed tagline). \n\n• Edited AD-Selfie should be framed in hard copy (A2/A3) with Matt finishing.\n\n• Submission should be done on stipulated date.\n\n</string>

    <string name="title_activity_m5">BIZTECH</string>
    <string name="m5desp">Quiz based on business news, technology news, basic to high level concepts of management and engineering, identify companies by logo and taglines, based on sports, bollywood and general knowledge</string>
    <string name="m5rules">• Only team entries are eligible. \n\n• A team shall consist of 3 (three) participants.\n\n• The decision of the quiz-master will be final and will not be subjected to any change.\n\n• The participants shall not be allowed to  use mobile or other electronic gadgets.\n\n• Audience  shall  not give any hints or clues to the competitors.\n\n• Replacement of any participant  of a team is not allowed after registration.\n\n• </string>

    <string name="title_activity_m6">WRIST WRESTLING</string>
    <string name="m6desp">Various factors can play a part in one\'s success in arm wrestling. Technique and overall arm strength are the two greatest contributing factors to winning an arm wrestling match.</string>
    <string name="m6rules">• The competitors shoulders must be square to the table before the match start\n\n• To make a winning pin you must touch your opponent to the touch pad.\n\n• The competitors shoulder can not go past the center of the table.\n\n• If the referee has to stop the match a second time for the \'hurt arm\' position the match will be awarded to his opponent.\n\n• all referee decisions are final.\n\n</string>

    .<string name="title_activity_m7">Fun Race</string>
    <string name="m7desp">Fun race is an event in which contestants run in a pair, through a set of course, tackling obstacles.</string>
    <string name="m7rules">•Participant must registered themselves at registration desk.\n\n• Only two members are allowed in a team.\n\n• Participants have to complete all the task as per sequence.\n\n• Together, they race to the finish line.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_k1">FASHION FUSION</string>
    <string name="k1desp">\“Fashion is not something that exists in dresses only. Fashion is in the sky, in the street, fashion has to do with ideas, the way we live, what is happening.\”\n\nFashion is an extension of personality. It gives a certain amount of freedom to people and allows them to be who they want to be. It is a chance to be like everybody and the one at the same time.\n\nLitmus presents FASHION FUSION for all the fashion lovers to walk the runway with their head held up high. So take a deep breath, focus on a point in distance, and go! </string>
    <string name="title_activity_k2">DANCELLENIUM</string>
    <string name="k2desp">Dance is the hidden language of the soul.\n\nDancing with feet is one thing, and dancing with heart is another, it\’s a conversation between the body and the soul.\n\nLitmus is a refreshing stage for the dance lovers here the students just get along with it, it\’s a poem of which every movement is a word.\n\nSo put on your dancing shoes and just kick the stage hard, let the spectators be on their feet and the applause carry you around!\n\nJust dance like no one\’s watching, and remember Dance to express!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_k3">CURTAIN UP</string>
    <string name="k3desp">\“Acting is not a state of being, but a state of appearing to be!\”\n\nThey say play is not in the words or lines, it\’s in the soul and the heart. Litmus gives platform to our gripped and smart actors, to perform and exhibit their true interim.\n\nActs which are just robust and thoughtful, with a message and meaning spread at the end to the audience.\n\nDramas are the mirror, a sharp reflection of society.\n\nAs we say the world is the stage, so let\’s lay on some sweats!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_k4">SOUND AT SIGHT AND UNPLUGGED</string>
    <string name="k4desp">\“Music gives soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination and life to everything\”.\n\nWhen words fail music speaks. Sound at sight and unplugged are such platforms for the soothing voices of the university. An event to give the calmness to the mind and soul to the audience, an experience one would love to have.\n\nThese events will leave you mesmerized with its budding performers. So enjoy these performances and lose yourself in music!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registerp">Registration Panel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registerm">Magnif Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registerc">Chakravyuh Registration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registerk">Register for Kalakriti</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registermenu">Register Your Self For</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notify">"Notifications Center "</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fire_base_example">FireBase Example</string>

    <string name="dates_technovision">Date : 9 &amp; 10 MAR 2017 </string>
    <string name="dates_magnif">Date : 9 &amp; 10 MAR 2017</string>
    <string name="dates_sports">Dates : 6 MAR 2017</string>
    <string name="dates_sports_earlybird">Dates : 28 FEB 2017</string>
    <string name="dates_sports_onspot">Dates : 1 MAR 2017</string>
    <string name="dates_kalakriti">Dates : 11 MAR 2017</string>


</resources>
